what one of the unemployment that
qué te una de las desocupacion que más
touched me the most and I'm going to explain it to you here
me tocaron y os la voy a explicar aquí
because I've already explained it on some
porque ya la he explicado en algún
program in some podcast where people were
programa en algún podcast que la gente
throwing their hands up in the air and
se echaba las manos a la cabeza y me
saying to me but how were you able to do it Look the
decía pero cómo has podido hacer Mira el
first year I went to vacate alone with
primer año yo iba a desocupar solo con
a friend of mine because at first I didn't
un amigo mío porque yo al principio no
have any money there were two of us a guy who was a very good
tenía dinero íbamos dos un tío muy buen
friend of mine a total boxer we went to a
amigo mío un boxeador total fuimos a un
farm in the suburbs and to vacate some unaccompanied
a una finca al rabal y a desocupar unos
minors and there were five unaccompanied minors I think there were
menas y había cinco menas creo que eran
and they came out there shirtless everything what
y salieron ahí sin camiseta todo qué
boss I don't know what I don't know how much Of course at
jefe no sé qué no sé cuánto Claro en
that time nobody knew who
aquella época nadie sabía quién era
unccompanied minors were and no matter how much they said we
desocupa y por mucho que dijera
were just starting out and while I was
estábamos empezando y mientras yo me
arguing with come on you have to
discutía con venga que tenéis que
clean up I hear help help help the voice of
recoger oigo ayuda ayuda ayuda la voz de
a girl obviously I hit her I
una niña yo obviamente le pegué le pegué
pushed the first unaccompanied minor that was
un empujón al primer Mena que había por
there I ran towards where
ahí me metí corriendo para donde venían
those screams were coming from and I found a girl in her
esos gritos y me encontré a una niña en
panties covered in a mattress on the
braguitas tapada en un colchón en el
floor with a blonde Caucasian Spanish woman
suelo con una mana española caucásica y
Okay I don't care about that I say to her
rubia Vale que eso me da igual le digo
What do you  it happened and he says to me I knew
Qué te ha pasado y me dice yo conocía a
one of these guys from the neighborhood I had arranged to meet
uno de estos del barrio había quedado
him and when I got there there were five of them and I said so
con él y cuando he llegado eran cinco y
what happened he says well with
digo Y qué ha pasado me dice pues con
the five of them what did I do I said do you want to report do you want to report he
los cinco qué hice le dije quieres
said no
denunciar quieres denunciar me dijo no
because I know them from here in the neighborhood they
porque los conozco de aquí del barrio
were from Barceloneta and such I say Okay do
eran de la Barceloneta y tal digo Bueno
n't worry I'll get you out of here the kid got
no te preocupes te saco de aquí la cría
dressed I walked by and they were
se vistió yo pasé por delante y y se
laughing eh don't take our girlfriend I
reían eh no te lleves a nuestra novia
say no no yeah I'll be right back I'll be right
digo no no si yo ahora vengo yo ahora
back Don't worry I told my friend
vuelvo No te preocupes a mi colega le
not to close the door don't
dije que no cierren la puerta que no
close the door he stayed there I went
cierren la puerta se quedó allí bajé
downstairs I took her up a taxi and up the first
abajo la subí un taxi y subí la primera
sentence he said to me when I got to the
frase que me soltó cuando llegué a la
door you know what he said to me the first one who
puerta sabes lo que me dijo el primero
didn't finish the sentence obviously boss you
que no acabó la frase obviamente jefe
have a sister for me he didn't finish the
Tienes una hermana para mí no acabó la
sentence we were in that apartment for 5 hours no
frase estuvimos 5 horas en ese piso no
no I'm just I'll tell you one thing and I'll
no Yo es que a m Yo te digo una cosa y
tell you one thing there were few hours we
te digo una cosa pocas eran las horas
were there teaching them our
que estuvimos allí enseñándoles nuestras
customs let's say that okay but
costumbres vamos a decir eso vale pero
everyone is a father has a nephew
todo el mundo es padre tiene sobrin
has sisters No no it's not that but it's  which is that it
tiene hermanas No no es que pero es que
is something unheard of I mean how
es que es algo inaudito o sea cómo se
can a father feel when
puede sentir un padre que le violan a
a girl is raped and they don't put them in jail
una niña y que no les meten en la cárcel
well you go look for them You
pues tú los vas a buscar Vu loco Yo me
're crazy I'm going crazy You're not going to look for him and you
vuelvo loco No lo vas a buscar y
start by cutting off his balls then the
empiezas cortándole los huevos luego la
[ __ ] I'll ruin myself but in a way I'm
poll yo me arruino pero de una manera yo
very sorry I know it's going to sound really
lo siento mucho sé que va a sonar muy
bad and people are going to say look this
mal y la gente va a decir fíjate este
fascist no s it affects me
fascista no s a mí me toca
but it's not fascist let's see It's
pero es que eso no es fascista a ver Es
that I would seek my ruin I would seek my
que yo me buscaría la ruina me buscaría
ruin with a Spaniard you look for him and if he
la ruina con un español lo buscas y si
doesn't do justice to your country and the law
no le hace justicia a tu país y la ley
if the law doesn't give him justice you give it to him
si la ley no le da justicia se la das tú
I'm very sorry the problem
yo lo siento mucho es que el problema
Fran also as you say is that if
Fran además como tú bien dices es que si
you tell me that later they catch him and they
tú me dices que luego lo pillan y les
put them in 30 years or they cut off his [ __ ] and
meten 30 años o le cortan la [__] y se
put it in his mouth I'll buy it but I'll
la meten en la boca te lo compro pero es
give you an example And this is real there were
que te pongo un ejemplo Y esto es real
also some attacks Well one
también había unas agresiones Bueno un
day on a program from Catalonia
día en un programa de de de Cataluña
a journalist came out  doors of the
salía un periodista a las puertas de los
courts where they released those
juzgados donde soltaban a los a los
arrested during those 48 hours the journalist
detenidos durante esos 48 la periodista
was there waiting to see who would come out
estaba allí esperando a ver quién salía
well a group of unaccompanied minors come out who had
bueno sale un grupo de menas que Habían
tried to sexually assault a girl
intentado agredir sexualmente a una cría
I think they managed to penetrate her one but
creo que la pudieron penetrar uno pero
not all three three came out Okay when they
no los tres salían tres Vale cuando
stabbed the boyfriend I mean Sorry they
apuñalaron al novio o sea Perdona
stabbed the boyfriend and slept with her
apuñalaron al novio y se la zumbaron
in front of the boyfriend Okay when the
delante del novio Vale cuando llegó la
police arrived they also tried to stab the
policía intentaron también apuñalar a la
police the concurrence of crimes are eh
policía el concurso de delitos son eh
Well a crime of injury or attempted
Bueno un delito de lesiones o tentativa
sexual assault and resisting
agresión sexual y resistencia a la
arrest okay since there are three they
autoridad vale como son tres se les
can be included in this criminal organization
puede meter a esta organización criminal
in 48 hours these men would walk
en 48 horas estos señores se salían en
free still high from the queue and
libertad todavía colocados de la cola y
come out saying buh tonight we're going
salían diciendo bu esta noche nos vamos
to [ __ ] someone else how embarrassing what are you
a [__] a otra qué vergüenza qué
trying to do that's the problem The problem is that
pretendes es el problema El problema es
you what [ __ ] message are you
ese tú qué [__] mensaje les estás
sending them like I mean to me that judge
enviando como o sea a mí ese juez que me
tells me you don't have a daughter you see those
diga usted no tiene hija usted ve a esos
three animals those three [ __ ] animals
tres animales esos tres [__] animales
that are telling you that the commission of
que le están diciendo que la comisión de
crimes are stabbing
delitos son apuñalamiento agresión
sexual assault resisting arrest and you're
sexual resistencia a la autoridad y los
going to leave them  in freedom when he knows
va a dejar en libertad cuando sabe
perfectly well that they are this type of
perfectamente que son este tipo de
profile that then arrest them and say 50 criminal
perfil que luego los detienen y dicen 50
records How come 50 criminal records
antecedentes Cómo que 50 antecedentes
dima we here to pay in Thailand
dima nosotros aquí a pagar en Tailandia
had to be Fran it's curious it's
tenían que estar Fran es que es curioso
curious because not a single
es curioso porque es que no viene ni una
woman comes Not a single baby comes Not even a no
mujer No viene ni un bebé No viene ni un
no all young people of military age I
no no todos jóvenes en edad militar a mí
find it curious that
me resulta curioso que que venga que
people fleeing the war come and only
venga gente huyendo de la guerra y solo
men flee [ __ ] if it were like
huyan hombres [__] si fuera como
Ukraine here we have welcomed a lot of
Ucrania aquí hemos acogido un montón de
Ukrainian refugees and almost all of them were
refugiados ucranianos y casi todas eran
women and children while the men
mujeres y niños mientras los hombres
were at war however Here there is
estaban en la guerra sin embargo Aquí
a war and all the
hay una guerra y se vienen todos los
men come and they leave the women there [ __ ]
hombres y dejan a las mujeres allí no
what a [ __ ] strange war
[__] qué [__] guerra más rara A mí que
Tell me what the [ __ ] war is in
me digan qué [__] guerra hay en
Morocco is that I'm already at the
Marruecos es que estoy ya está a la
tip of the [ __ ] I swear I'm at
punta del cipote te lo juro estoy está
the tip of the tail here we have to bring in
la punta del rabo aquí hay que meter a
all of [ __ ] Africa we have to bring in all of [ __ ] Africa
toda la [__] África hay que meter en
because if not neither
España a toda [__] África porque si no
the peper nor the
no están contentos ni la peper ni los
socialists nor all the [ __ ]
socialistas ni toda la [__] cochambre
communist and red filth that we have in this
comunista y roja que tenemos en este
shitty country will be happy what I said before
país de [__] yo lo que he dicho antes
If it were up to me I would not close the
si de mí dependiera Yo no cerraría los
centers for unaccompanied minors, I would not close them, I would
centros de menas no los cerraría yo
put one next to the house of every
pondría uno al lado de la casa de cada
politician who is in favor of this and let them
político que está a favor de esto y que
suffer the consequences when their daughter is
sufra las consecuencias cuando a su hija
scared, one of these children who
la de un sustito uno de estos niños que
comes fleeing the war when they
viene huyendo de la guerra cuando se
find themselves with a knife or a machete
encuentren con una navaja con un machete
or they do to them what we all know, let them
o les hagan lo que todos sabemos que
continue saying that they are children who come
sigan diciendo que son niños que vienen
from the war, of course solidarity
de la guerra per claro la solidaridad
is very good with other people's money
está muy bien con el dinero de los demás
and in other people's neighborhoods it is very
y en los barrios de los demás está muy
good eh It is very good to defend that unaccompanied minors come
bien eh Está muy bien defender que
while you live in La
vengan menas mientras tú vives en la
Moraleja or in La Finca There it is very good to
moraleja o en la finca Ahí está muy bien
defend all this while those who
defender todo esto mientras los que lo
suffer while those who suffer the robberies the muggings the
sufren mientras los que sufren los robos
machete blows are those who
los atracos los machetazos son los que
live in the working class neighborhoods in the
viven en los barrios obreros en los
humble neighborhoods that are fed up with
barrios Humildes que están hasta los
it already put a [ __ ] center for unaccompanied minors
[__] ya poner un [__] centro de menas
next to La Moraleja next to
al lado de en la moraleja al lado de la
Feijo's [ __ ] house put a
[__] casa de feijo poner un centro de
menn center next to the ruffian's house
menín al lado de la casa de rufian al
next to the house of  Yolanda Daz in El
lado de la casa de Yolanda Díaz en el
Retiro in La Moncloa no, you don't put them there, you
retiro en la moncloa no ahí no los
don't put them in Vallecas, you put them
ponéis no los ponéis en vallecas los
in the
ponéis en la ponéis en los barrios más
humblest neighborhoods so that the workers eat them, you
Humildes Para que se los coman los
piece of [ __ ], what are you
trabajadores pedazo de [__] qué es lo
all politicians who are in
que sois todos los políticos que están a
favor of this, let's not forget what
favor de esto que no se nos olvide qu
you say one of the crimes that
dices tú uno de los delitos con los que
these people are coming out with that you're telling us
sale esta gente que nos estás contando
Dani is sexual assault, let's not
Dani es agresión sexual que no se nos
forget that they just charged the same
olvide que acaban de meterle el mismo
crime to a guy who gave a [ __ ] to a
delito a un tío que le dio un pico a una
colleague at work, but what is that with
colega del trabajo pero qué es eso con
the [ __ ]
la [__]
lions, crazy, I don't understand how there aren't
leones loco Yo no entiendo como no hay
more murders in Spain, and I'm telling you more,
más asesinatos en España y más te lo
eh, from here I encourage all the
digo eh yo desde aquí animo a todos los
parents, I think they rape your daughter and they
padres yo pienso te violan a la hija y
rape your daughter and justice doesn't
te violan a la hija y la justicia no te
give you justice, stop [ __ ] around, I don't trust
da justicia déjate de hostias no confío
justice if justice doesn't do
en la justicia si la justicia no hace
justice, I don't have time to report
justi a mí no me da tiempo denunciar
it, take it myself, I would do it 100%. Also, there's
Tómatela yo yo lo haría 100% Yo además
time, for example here in Spain.
da tiempo por ejemplo aquí en España
Well, in the end, we try to be obedient in
Bueno yo al final intentamos se duar en
all the  causes of the grandparents
todas las causas de los abuelos
you will remember the case of Pepe Lomas the
recordaréis el caso de Pepe Lomas el
grandfather who defended himself in Ciudad
abuelo que se defendió de la en Ciudad
Real the one who was bleeding No yes that
real el que iba sangrentado No sí que
with Bueno they came at him with one the guy the
con Bueno le entraron con una el tío el
guy who has more criminal records grabbed a
tío que lleva más antecedentes cogi una
chainsaw and the man Obviously
moto sierra y el hombre Obviamente le
shot him twice But the thing is that I am very good
pegó dos tiros Pero es que yo soy muy
friends with Samuel Vzquez of a police force
amigo de Samuel Vázquez de una policía
for the 20th century that Ah okay the grandfather
para el siglo XX que Ah vale el abuelo
from prison Okay in the end AB came out
de la carcel Vale al final salió AB
free he wasn't grandfather No yes but because
suelto no fue abuelto No sí pero porque
we did we organized a demonstration
hicimos montamos una manifestación
in the center of Madrid we
nosotros en el centro de Madrid hicimos
campaigned and in the end it was achieved okay
campaña y al final se consiguió vale
But that man spent months in prison no that
Pero ese hombre pasó meses en prisión no
man should have been given
a ese hombre le tenían que haber dado
a [ __ ] medal a medal and Samuel
una [__] medalla una medalla y Samuel lo
says it clearly the one who enters my house
dice claramente el que entra en mi casa
at 3 in the morning where
a las 3 de la madrugada donde está
my wife and my two daughters are sleeping Me
durmiendo mi mujer y mis dos hijas Yo
as a policeman and I as a gun license
como policía y yo como licencia de armas
that I have I empty the [ __ ] magazine
que tengo yo le vacío el [__] cargador
into my daughter's room you don't arrive dude I'll
al habitación de mi hija no llegas tío
take your life I'll take it away and then I
te quito la vida te la quito y luego
condemn it what's my turn but my daughter and my
condeno que me toca pero mi hija y mi
wife will still be alive or at least I'll give
mujer seguirán viva o al menos le daré
these sons of their mother a hard time but you  I
guerra a estos hijos de su madre pero te
say the same thing. Let's see, that's
digo lo mismo A ver eso es que es una es
what you're saying, but when I'm talking about
lo que dices tú pero yo hablando de la
occupation, I can't imagine
ocupación Yo es que no me puedo imaginar
that you. For example, let's say I
que tú Por ejemplo yo vamos a decir que
work, I don't know
trabajo yo que sé en un carrefour no sé
if there's a Carrefour there in Spain. Well, I
si hay carrefour ahí en España bueno
pay taxes, okay, I don't get involved in
pago el impuesto vale no me meto en
crimes, I don't do anything wrong. I buy a
delitos no hago nada malo me compro una
house, okay, it's going well for me, I try to buy another one
casa eh me va bien intento comprar otra
and I rent it out, okay, or I don't rent it out or I don't
y la alquilo vale o no la alquilo o no
rent it out and there, and there I feel like putting up
la alquil y allí y allí me da por poner
memories of my family. I don't live there,
los recuerdos de mi familia no vivo allí
but I feel like putting up photos, clothes
pero me da por poner las fotos la ropa
of my children when they were little, all of
de mis niños cuando eran pequeños todo
this. No, they don't get into me there and I'm
esto no a mí me entran ahí y lo siento
very sorry, I'm not inciting crime.
mucho yo no estoy incitando al delito
But if they get into your things, you go in with
Pero si te entran a por las cosas entras
blows and then you go to jail, they're
los a hostias y luego vas para la cárcel
not going to be able to put
no van a poder meter en la cárcel a
650,000 people in jail, right? That's it. Look, just
650,000 personas no eso eso Mira tal
like you said it, we were talking about it in a, in
como tú lo dices lo hablábamos en un en
one, because sometimes I, uh, since I have
una porque yo a veces ya eh Como tengo
so much experience, it's not that I already give
tanta experiencia no es que yo ya doy
talks at police stations or police stations
charlas en comandancias o en comisarías
to explain my experiences.
para para explicar mis experiencias los
legal tricks that I have and that uh I
trucos legales que tengo yd y eso eh lo
was talking about it with a group of civil guards
hablaba con un grupo de guardias civiles
and they told me that very thing Frank they
y me decían eso precisamente Frank ellos
told me if here in Spain there was a
me decían si aquí en España hubiera una
Revolution and everything look Ah Frank it's
Revolución y toda fíjate Ah Frank lo
over every person who has an
acabado toda persona que tenga un piso
occupied apartment takes five friends and I'll
ocupado coge a cinco amigos y es te
give you an example you have seen
pongo un ejemplo vosotros habéis visto
the movie The Purge Well
la la película de La purga No pues
imagine me or Fran we have quite a few
imagínate yo o Fran que tenemos bastante
people who follow us on social media I'll make a
gente que nos sigue en redes yo hago un
video tomorrow and I say good Spaniards
vídeo mañana y digo españoles de bien
Tomorrow at 12 o'clock at night sharp
Mañana a las 12 de la noche en punto
every owner who goes with five
cada propietario que vaya con cinco
friends and a May to recover their
amigos y un mayo para recuperar sus
properties there won't be a police force that
propiedades no va a haber policía que
can stop us all it would be great the
nos pueda parar a todos sería la [__]
ideal thing would be that they do it right with the law
lo ideal es que lo hagan bien con la ley
and with I mean let's pass the law and let it be
y con O sea que que saque leye y que sea
logical Jai it doesn't matter but there comes a
lo lógico Jai no interesa pero llega un
time but let's see if there comes
momento pero vamos a ver si es que llega
a time what Dani was saying
un momento lo que lo que estaba diciendo
about the menas is that there comes a
Dani de los de los menas es que llega un
time man that you how do you live in one
momento tío que tú cómo vives en un
place because there are people who
sitio porque es que hay gente que a lo
maybe live in the Raval and can't go anywhere else I
mejor vive en el raval y no se puede ir
want to express all my
a otro sitio quiero expresar toda mi
solidarity with the neighbors of sopuerta
solidaridad con los vecinos de sopuerta
who are suffering the consequences of
que están sufriendo las consecuencias de
having installed a center for unaccompanied minors
que hayan instalado un centro de menas e
in their area and are demonstrating and
en su zona y se están manifestando y ya
are already criminalizing oles Well, from
están criminalizando oles Pues yo desde
here I want to give you all my support, I
aquí les quiero dar todo mi apoyo les
ask you to be brave, to keep
pido que sean valientes que sigan
pushing because in the end between us all we
apretando que al final entre todos
will manage to solve this and you have to go
conseguiremos solucionar esta y tiene
down every day, go down the
que bajar todos los días baja la
stairs you don't know what you're going to
escalera no saben lo que se va a
find, you have to accompany
encontrar tiene que acompañar a todos
everyone when I [ __ ] on my [ __ ] life
los lados cuando me cago en mi [__] vida
what Roberto vaquero says eh he says he
lo que dice Roberto vaquero eh dice que
's a communist but Roberto vaquero is more
es comunista pero Roberto vaquero es más
fascist than Franco I tell you he speaks it's
facha que Franco te digo é habla es
true damn he talks about recovering the
verdad [__] él habla de recuperar los
neighborhoods let's recover our
barrios vamos a recuperar nuestros
neighborhoods so that our families can
barrios que nuestras familias puedan
walk so that our grandmothers can
caminar que nuestras abuelas puedan
our mothers damn It's normal that
nuestras madres [__] Es lo normal que
when we were dwarfs look Roberto and I
cuando éramos enanos fíjate Roberto y yo
politically we are at the no maybe at
políticamente estamos en las no quizás
antipodes because politically I also do
en las antípodas porque yo además
n't like to take a
políticamente no me gusta mucho
position but but we have coned We
posicionarme pero pero hemos conado Nos
write to each other sometimes and we have many
escribimos a veces y tenemos muchas
things in common in fact we might prepare
cosas en común de hecho igual preparamos
something together okay without explaining
una cosita juntos vale sin explicar
now well what in the end what
ahora bien el qué total al final lo que
Roberto vaquero explains is
explica Roberto vaquero es de sentido
common sense it's not left nor
común no es de izquierdas ni es de
right it's Spain it's been Spain all your
derechas es España es España toda la
[ __ ] life it's that it's been Spain all your [ __ ]
[__] vida es que es España toda la [__]
life it's that you went down to the children they
vida es que te bajabas a los niños nos
threw us out into the [ __ ] street and you were in the
tiraban a la [__] calle y estabas en la
street and the guy from the bar came and
calle y te venía el del bar y te echaba
scolded you and you went home again and you
la bronca y te ibas para casa otra vez y
were calm and the and people walked
estabas tranquilo y la y la gente iba
calmly in the street or yes yes at
tranquila por la calle o que sí que sí
that time they talked about the knife-wielding Ugh
aquella época se hablaba del navajero Uf
the knife-wielding Yes but the worst it was or
el navajero Sí pero lo máximo que era o
the worst that happened to you was the junkie from
lo máximo que te pasaba era el yonky de
your neighborhood for that with the knife and you
tu barrio por es con el cuchillo y le
slapped him and he left because of that but
dabas un guantazo y se iba por eso pero
now you can't there are people
es que ahora no puedes es que hay gente
who can't and it's been almost a year in
que no puede y lleva casi un año en el
which it hadn't been processed if minor or
que no se había tramitado si menor o
adult the wine from the juvenile center
mayor el vino del centro de menores el
last month but how old are you?
mes pasado pero cuántos años tienes yo
The ones from Africa caught me, the
me prendieron los de África los de
real ones 22 years old 22 and you had entered as a
verdad 22 años 22 y habías entrado como
minor sometimes when the
menor a veces cuando llega aquí el
juvenile center arrives here when there is no person it's going to
centro menor cuando no hay persona es va
come here it's mandatory you are a minor you are a minor you are a minor they
a venir aquí obligatorio tú eres menor
tell you to
tú eres menor eres menor te dicen que
say  that you are a minor this force when you
digas que eres menor este fuerza cuando
arrive from the Minor Center it will be a test
lleg de Centro menor va a ser prueba
then your adult will be out
después tu mayor a la [__]
on the [ __ ] street I mean but here everyone is of legal age Yes in Barcelona in Barcelona obviously the number of crimes is hidden and camouflaged and they equate a sexual assault or a stabbing to a robbery or a threat so that the statistics go down a bit No but in Barcelona before they would put a
en Barcelona antes pues eso te ponían un
knife to your side just like now they are going up
cuchillo tal igual ahora están subiendo
to Paseo de Gracia to steal watches stabbing people I mean
a Paseo de gracia a robar relojes
before they would say
pegando puñaladas o sea antes te decían
give me the watch or I'll stab you now they stab you
Dame el reloj o te pincho ahora te meten
eight times and then they take your
ocho puñaladas y luego te quitan el
watch it's crazy it's an arrangement
reloj es que es de loco es un arreglo
everything is a business
todo es un negocio
guys for me yes Ah for you I mean I
chicos para m sí Ah para ti o sea yo lo
see it very clearly moment that the
veo clarísimo momento que los
Venezuelans won't even try to steal
venezolanos ni mojera a robarles el
jobs from the Canaries it's a lie here they are
trabajo a los canarios mentira aquí son
some lazy pieces of [ __ ] that the government
unos vagos de [__] que el gobierno
maintains with a ton of aid that
mantiene con con un montón de ayudas que
in my country that doesn't exist in my country Either you
en mi país eso no existe en mi país O
work or you die of hunger there is no
trabajas o te mueres de hambre no hay de
other way That's
otra Así es
easy for me the Canaries not all the
fácil para mí los canarios no todos los
Canaries yes those who  They complain about those of us who
canarios sí los que se quejan de los que
come from outside, I've seen videos in
venimos de afuera yo he visto vídeos en
Barcelona and attacks where in this
Barcelona y agresiones donde en este
case I explain why
caso yo en este caso lo explico porque
I gave him a lawyer and I sent him to
yo le puse el abogado y yo lo envié a
prison okay, a security guard came out
prisión vale salió un vigilante de
in a media case where he was
seguridad en un caso mediático donde le
prohibited from entering in this case he was
prohíbe la entrada en este caso era
Dominican because he was Dominican end
dominicano porque era dominicano fin
okay the Dominican the
vale el dominicano el vigilante
security guard from the subway kicks him out the Dominican goes
seguridad metro lo echa el dominicano va
home puts on a balaclava grabs
a su casa se pone un pasamontañas coge
the knife Oh and comes back yes that's true and
el cuch Ah y vuelve sí es verdad eso y
stabs him in
le apuñada por la espalda escúchame así
the back listen to me like that Fran twice that is at least attempted homicide if not murder okay why with treachery why does he do the act of going home to get the gun come cover himself wait for the moment where the other was or rather that in
donde el otro estaba o sea eso en
any other country it's 30 years here the
cualquier otro país son 30 años aquí el
subway guard the subway didn't even give him a
vigilante de metro el metro no le puso
lawyer he made a call and I
ni abogado él hizo un llamamiento y yo
belong to private security I
como pertenezco a a la seguridad privada
am a security guard escort
que soy director de seguridad de escolta
I gave him my lawyer and we put him in jail
yo le puse mi abogado y lo metimos preso
and recently he got paid  the compensation I think
y hace poco ha cobrado la indemnización
was 9000 that he thanked me for he
creo que era 9000 que él me lo agradecía
said to me Look Dani Thank you very much
me decía Mira Dani Muchísimas gracias
that guy could have been killed with two
ese tío lo podían haber matado de dos
stab wounds in the back with the first
puñaladas en la espalda con la primera
intervention of the squad mosus he was
intervención de mosus de escuadra fue
released after 48 hours until
puesto en libertad las 48 horas hasta
my lawyer presented an
que mi abogado no presentó una
extension of the complaint with the with
ampliación de la denuncia con las con
the following evidence statements
con las siguientes pruebas declaraciones
and testimonies and all that we got
y testimonios y todo eso conseguimos que
that guy to go to prison but I mean you
ese tío fuera prisión pero o sea tú
stab someone in the back twice to
pegas dos puñaladas por la espalda para
kill a guy and the judge lets you go
matar a un tío Y te deja el juez en
and classifies it as a crime
libertad y te lo tipifica de un delito
of assault what the [ __ ] assault is an
de lesiones qué [__] lesiones es una
attempt at a crazy book of a crazy man
tentativa de libro loco de loco hombre
Of course what do you intend with these
Claro que que pretende con esas
attacks ent al al menda this What
agresiones ent al al al menda este Qué
message do you send when you stab
mensaje le envías cuando le pegas dos
a guy in the back twice and you
puñaladas a un tío por la espalda y
're 48 hours well as soon as I get out I'll
estás 48 horas pues cuanto salga le
put four in him I'll rape his girlfriend
meteré cuatro me violaré a la novia
the police will come and I'll try to
vendrá el policía y le Le intentaré
stab him too and then when I get out
apuñalar también y luego cuando salga
of the weekend the [ __ ] Pedro Snchez will
del fin de semana el Pedro Sánchez de
give me a full payment
los [__] me dará una paga total